{
    "id": "b012cdcbc6684538a05579bb729cb86c",
    "title": "Prepositions Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "Who is that cute girl ..................................... the fifth row?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "on",
                "in",
                "at"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "da7bc456e8d3440f850bcf283dcd0752"
        },
        {
            "question": "There is a big spider ..................................... the ceiling.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "on",
                "at"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "82c7caf8a68148a59ff79cc5f6e717b8"
        },
        {
            "question": "Granny is arriving ................................... the 30 train.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "on",
                "at"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "56b60ad1610d40c19b618c79c745d2c7"
        },
        {
            "question": "As there was no room on the bus, we got .......................................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "out",
                "off",
                "up"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "875b626d06c64d2c80b9dbef5348648f"
        },
        {
            "question": "Don’t throw food ...................................... the animals.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "for",
                "to",
                "at"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "dacd08ea7f8b4bf89dcde93374b1f083"
        },
        {
            "question": "We should arrive ..................................... Smith’s in time for dinner.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "on",
                "at"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "6c9f3000b25e45bca56319d7a60d7943"
        },
        {
            "question": "She lives in a flat ................................... the third floor.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "on",
                "at"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "379fb7d240f0401290973cac0f21f4b3"
        },
        {
            "question": "What did you do .................................... the weekend?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "at",
                "on",
                "in"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "f3bd289f4db044538a04427965c2239a"
        },
        {
            "question": "He can run 1000 meters ................................. about four minutes.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "at",
                "in"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "2ad68a7a165c457abbf2ef7691280210"
        },
        {
            "question": "I met her .................................... a cold afternoon in winter.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "at",
                "on"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "e6d9cd647b1147c899f1b712dd49145f"
        }
    ]
}